Just like Adobe Illustrator, Inkscape is a vector graphics editing program. But Inkscape
就像Adobe Illustrator一样，Inkscape是一款非矢量图形编辑程序。但Inkscape
is 100% free! With Inkscape, as with illustrator, you can create logos, illustrations and artwork.
是100%免费的！使用Inkscape，就像使用Illustrator一样，您可以创建徽标、插图和艺术品。
Because the graphics made in Inkscape are vector based, you can scale them
因为在Inkscape中制作的图形是基于矢量的，所以您可以对它们进行缩放
infinitely without losing quality. So let's download Inkscape. I go to: www.inkscape.org.
无限而不失品质。那么，让我们先下载Inkscape吧。我的网址是：www.inkscape e.org。
On the Inkscape website you can find a lot of information and resources.
在Inkscape网站上，你可以找到很多信息和资源。
The latest version is 1.2, but there already is a contest for the new screen for Inkscape 1.3.
最新版本是1.2，但Inkscape 1.3的新屏幕已经有竞争了。
I click on: ''Download Now!''. Inkscape tells me I've been redirected to the best download,
我点击：“立即下载！”Inkscape告诉我，我被重定向到了最好的下载，
which in my case is a ''Windows Installer Package''. ''MSI'' stands for ''Microsoft Software
在我的例子中，它是一个“Windows Installer和Package”。‘’MSI‘’代表‘’微软软件
Installer'', which is normally used to install and update software on Windows. The Microsoft
Installer‘’，通常用于在Windows上安装和更新软件。微软
installer keeps track of which products have been installed, and to which location. This means with
Installer会跟踪哪些产品已经安装，以及安装到了哪个位置。这意味着使用
an update of the software, it can detect the older version, and can preserve any custom settings or
作为软件的更新，它可以检测到较旧的版本，并可以保留任何自定义设置或
configurations that I applied. I click on it to start the download. In my Downloads folder
我应用的配置。我点击它，开始下载。在我的下载文件夹中
I double-click on the MSI file. I click on: Next. Here I can see where Inkscape will be installed.
我双击MSI文件。我点击：下一步。在这里我可以看到Inkscape将安装在哪里。
You can choose not to install some parts of Inkscape. But I like to have all extensions and
您可以选择不安装Inkscape的某些部分。但我喜欢所有的分机和
dictionaries. When asked if I want to proceed the installation, I click on: Yes. Then I click on:
词典。当被问及是否要继续安装时，我点击：是。然后我点击：
Finish. In the next lecture we'll look at how to customize the user interface of Inkscape.
完成。在下一堂课中，我们将了解如何定制Inkscape的用户界面。